const Questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "1) Which is the largest continent?",
    answer: ["Asia", "Africa", "Europe", "North America"],
    correctAnswer: "Asia",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "2) Which is the richest country in the world?",
    answer: ["US", "India", "Qatar", "Australia"],
    correctAnswer: "Qatar",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "3) Which is the national bird of India?",
    answer: ["Pigeon", "Peacock", "Sparrow", "Crow"],
    correctAnswer: "Peacock",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "4) Which crop is sown on the largest area in India?",
    answer: ["Rice", "Wheat", "Sugarcane", "Maize"],
    correctAnswer: "Rice",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "5) which is the national animal of India?",
    answer: ["Lion", "Tiger", "Elephant", "Giraffe"],
    correctAnswer: "Tiger",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "6) Fastest shorthand writer was?",
    answer: ["Dr.G.D.Bist", "J.R.D.Tata", "J.M.Tagore", "Khudada Khan"],
    correctAnswer: "Dr.G.D.Bist",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "7) Golf player Vijay Singh belongs to which country?",
    answer: ["USA", "Fiji", "India", "UK"],
    correctAnswer: "Fiji",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "8) First Afghan war took place in?",
    answer: ["1839", "1843", "1833", "1848"],
    correctAnswer: "1839",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "9) Federation Cup, World Cup, Allywyn International Trophy and Challenge Cup are awarded to winners of?",
    answer: ["Tennis", "Volleyball", "Basketball", "Cricket"],
    correctAnswer: "Volleyball",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "10) Gravity setting chambers are used in industries to remove?",
    answer: ["SOx", "NOx", "CO", "Suspended particulate matter"],
    correctAnswer: "Suspended particulate matter",
  },
];

export default Questions;
